import 'package:flutter/material.dart';
import 'package:qs_app/components/mcqs_content_box.dart';

class EteaBiologyContentScreen extends StatelessWidget {
  @override
  Widget build(BuildContext context) {
    return Scaffold(
      appBar: AppBar(
        title: Text('ETEA Biology'),
      ),
      body: SingleChildScrollView(
        child: Padding(
          padding: EdgeInsets.all(20.0),
          child: Column(
            children: [
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Amount of oxygen in expired air is?',
                option1: '21%',
                option2: '0.04%',
                option3: '4%',
                option4: '16%',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'In human and other higher animals, the exchange of gases is carried out by?',
                option1: 'Respiratory',
                option2: 'Air passageway',
                option3: 'Skin',
                option4: 'Lungs',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Power of speaking is only gifted to?',
                option1: 'Human being',
                option2: 'Crow',
                option3: 'Monkey',
                option4: 'Parrot',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'A thick muscular layer beneath lungs is called?',
                option1: 'Bladder',
                option2: 'Diaphragm',
                option3: 'Kidney',
                option4: 'Ureter',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'When the World no tobacco day is celebrated?',
                option1: '30-Jun',
                option2: '11-Jun',
                option3: '31-June',
                option4: '1-June',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'e',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'A cough, mild wheezing, fever chills and shortness of breath are symptoms of?',
                option1: 'Pneumonia',
                option2: 'Bronchitis',
                option3: 'Emphysema',
                option4: 'Asthma',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The rate of breathing during exercise or other hard:= physical work is?',
                option1: '20-30 times',
                option2: '40-50 times',
                option3: '20-40 times',
                option4: '30-40 times',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'No. of bronchi in the air passage way are?',
                option1: '3',
                option2: '4',
                option3: '2',
                option4: '1',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Glottis is a narrow opening at the floor of?',
                option1: 'Pharynx',
                option2: 'Antibiotics',
                option3: 'Nostril',
                option4: 'Nasal cavity',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'In human which process occurs in alveoli?',
                option1: 'Reproduction',
                option2: 'Transport',
                option3: 'Nutation',
                option4: 'Gaseous Exchange',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Where does the gaseous exchange occur in humans?',
                option1: 'Bronchi',
                option2: 'Trachea',
                option3: 'Alveoli',
                option4: 'Pharynx',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'In plants, gaseous exchange takes place as?',
                option1: 'CO2 and O2 both are absorbed',
                option2: 'CO2 is absorbed and O2 is removed',
                option3: 'CO2 and O2 both are removed',
                option4: 'CO2 is removed and O2 is absorbed',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The number of lobes in right lung is?',
                option1: '4',
                option2: '1',
                option3: '2',
                option4: '3',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Where does the gaseous exchange occur in humans?',
                option1: 'Larynx',
                option2: 'Trachea',
                option3: 'Pharynx',
                option4: 'Epiglottis',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'C-Shaped cartilaginous rings are present in the wall of?',
                option1: 'Alveoli',
                option2: 'Bronchi',
                option3: 'Trachea',
                option4: 'Bronchioles',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Most of the gaseous exchange in a leaf occurs through?',
                option1: 'Lenticels',
                option2: 'Stomata',
                option3: 'Cuticle',
                option4: 'General surface',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'Amount of nitrogen in expired air is?',
                option1: '70%',
                option2: '80%',
                option3: '4%',
                option4: '79%',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The percentage of oxygen from air which we inspired is?',
                option1: '21%',
                option2: '15%',
                option3: '28%',
                option4: '25%',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'a',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'For gaseous exchange the leaf and young stems have in their epidermis?',
                option1: 'Guard cells',
                option2: 'Lenticels',
                option3: 'Stomata',
                option4: 'Companion cell',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'The correct list of respiratory disorders is?',
                option1: 'Asthma, blood, cancer, emphysema, cholera',
                option2: 'Asthma, pneumonia, hemophilia, typhoid',
                option3: ' Asthma, pneumonia, hemophilia, malaria',
                option4: ' Asthma, emphysema, pneumonia, bronchitis ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'How many bronchi are there in the air passageway?',
                option1: ' One ',
                option2: 'Two',
                option3: 'Three',
                option4: 'Four',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' The normal breathing rate in human being is?',
                option1: '10-40 times per minute ',
                option2: '30-40 times per minute ',
                option3: '20-40 times per minute ',
                option4: '16-20 times per minute ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: 'All the alveoli of one side unite to form?',
                option1: ' Chest Box ',
                option2: ' Kidney ',
                option3: ' Lung ',
                option4: ' Thorax ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' Cartilage is absent in?',
                option1: ' trachea ',
                option2: ' bronchioles ',
                option3: ' bronchi ',
                option4: ' larynx ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' Which of the following is called voice box?',
                option1: ' Bronchi ',
                option2: ' Larynx ',
                option3: ' Alveoli ',
                option4: ' Trachea ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' The muscles of ribs are called?',
                option1: ' Cardiac muscles ',
                option2: ' Smooth muscles ',
                option3: ' Coastal muscles ',
                option4: ' Intercoastal muscles ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'd',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' Rate of breathing depends upon concentration of which gas?',
                option1: ' Hydrogen ',
                option2: ' Oxygen ',
                option3: ' Carbon dioxide ',
                option4: ' Nitrogen ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' In which of the following gaseous exchange occur through stomata?',
                option1: ' The aquatic plants ',
                option2: ' The leaves and young stems ',
                option3: ' Wood stems and nature roots ',
                option4: ' Young roots ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' The inflammation of bronchi or bronchioles is called?',
                option1: ' Chest box ',
                option2: ' Emphysema ',
                option3: ' Bronchitis ',
                option4: ' Pneumonia ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'c',
              ),
              McqsContentBox(
                question: ' The major cause of lungs cancer is?',
                option1: ' viral infection ',
                option2: ' nicotine ',
                option3: ' radiation ',
                option4: ' smoking ',
                option5: 'None of these',
                correctOption: 'b',
              ),
            ],
          ),
        ),
      ),
    );
  }
}


